Dude, it's him.
- Do you think it's actually true?
- Yeah right, stop bullshitting.
I'm gonna ask him.
Is the rumor, real?
Rumor?
We heard that Ahn Su-ho,
Yeon Si-eun, and you caught some gansters.
The Free Money guy.
Uh, uh-huh.
- Are you freaking serious?
- Oh, woah.
Yeah my friend lost millions
of won from that app.
So what happened? Tell us everything.
- Hey, Beom-seok-a, gimme your IG.
- You gotta tell us man, I'm dying to know.
Did you get home okay?
Yeah,
I did.
- You?
- I heard that Su-ho and Beom-seok got
- kidnapped, and Si-eun brought the police.
- I got home alright, too.
They're so freaking cool.
Alright.
You're gonna eat all that?
Yeah and then I'm going to the snack bar.
- Right, Oh Beom?
- Mhm.
- My treat, you should come.
- Nah, you always do.
Today it's my treat, get what you want.
It's going to be killer. Get ready.
Are you guys free this weekend?
I found this awesome restaurant.
Let's go.
Sounds like something I'd like.
I'm in.
Let's go.
Um, why talk about food
when you're eating?
What about you? You talk about life
while you're still living it.
Oh,
what about Yeong-i's job?
Her interview's this weekend.
We're short staffed so it works out.
- Who's Yeong-i?
- That girl.
The
one who bashed Gil-su on the head.
Oh.
Were you both already friends?
No.
Ah,
she's staying at Su-ho's
place for a while.
Should we invite her this weekend?
Sure,
that's fine with me. Yeah, invite her.
AHN SU-HO
FOLLOWING
YEONG-I
CHILLING AT HAN RIVER
DINNER WITH SU-HO'S GRANDMA
SI-EUN SURPRISED US WITH TASTY HAMBURGERS!
How is he?
Dad's
been busy.
The season.
Have you decided your path?
Not yet.
It's alright to take time to decide.
I'm not worried about your career path.
You're always good at everything.
There's a lot I can't do.
Hm?
Nothing.
Hey,
almost finished?
We can get coffee on our way.
I have a meeting.
Hello?
I'm on my way.
What do you wanna do on your birthday?
What do you think?
Nothing special.
We can meet up, have something to eat,
- Well, I could-
- yeah?
Watch it.
We can't just do nothing on your birthday.
We gotta have a lot of fun.
Ugh, we don't have to, ajumma-ya.
Oh when's your birthday?
Saturday two weeks from now.
Rent a party room?
Ajumma.
Aren't you saving money?
Huh?
I thought you were trying to rent a room.
- Yeah, that's our order.
- Agh, the menu's stacked.
What should I get?
What would you like?
Iced Americano for me.
I want
an iced Vienna.
Let's get a table.
This one looks good, right?
Come sit over here.
Would you like to order?
Hey, give me a thousand won.
- Don't have it.
- Yes please.
Here.
Hey, Si-eun-a!
Hey, hurry and come sit.
What? Why are you so dressed up today?
Did you think I'd be into that?
- You're so smart.
- Where have you been?
Hmm? You don't need to know.
I just had a thing.
A thing? What thing?
Hey,
- he's a super sus kinda guy.
- I already know where Si-eun's been.
Stop keeping track of me.
No way.
I have to watch to see when you get home.
Good idea. Check in on him.
- Do you know what WithMap is?
- No idea.
Hey, Oh Beom.
Hey.
WEAK HERO:
CLASS 1
- Want a drink?
- Hm?
- Sure,
should I come?
No, I'll go by myself.
Dang it.
Hey!
Oh Beom-seok.
- Oh Beom-seok?
- Hey!
Beom-seok? Why would he be here?
- Stop lying.
- It was him.
Stop shitting me. Don't lie.
- I really saw him.
- Hey, Beom-seok-a.
Shoot.
- Did he see us and run off?
- Beom-seok-jjang.
Beom-seok-a, where are you?
Beom-seok sings too?
Oh Beom-seok!
Hey, call his phone.
Shit.
Yeah, we're at karaoke.
The room number?
Dunno.
Hey, your friends keep calling you.
You stupid bitch, what the hell, huh?!
Why did you pick up my phone
without asking? Fuck.
Hey man, what's wrong?
Are you gonna hit me, or what?
- Fuck you.
- I will seriously fucking kill you.
Hey, that's enough.
What's with you, man?
- Beom-seok-a.
- You dumb fuck.
I said that's enough.
Fuck this, you stupid crazy asshole.
Fuck off.
Hey.
Hey!
I'll go after her.
Where are you going?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Fine.
Hey, Beom-seok-a.
- I told you that I saw him!
- Wow, my Beom-seok-jjang!
Fuck, you were right.
How've you been, Beom-seok-a?
- It's really been a while.
- Damn, man.
We missed you, dude.
We missed you, man.
What?
We're Beom-seok's friends.
We were talking.
It's just been so long,
we want to talk too.
Then do it later.
Sorry about that.
Let's hang soon.
I'll call you.
Make sure you pick up.
Let's go.
- See ya.
- See you later.
Man.
- Would've been fun.
- He still looks like a loser.
What was that?
Huh?
Those guys.
Oh.
It's no big deal.
Come on.
Oh, man.
His tongue's moving so fast
but he sounds like a freaking dumbass.
- You should do that all day.
- All day, every day.
Hey.
- Do it again, one more time.
- Dude, you're killing me.
Hey!
Quiet.
What's his problem?
- I was just trying to be funny.
- You were really funny.
Shut your mouths.
Did you laugh?
I didn't laugh.
I heard you laughing.
Do you want to die,
you fucking prick?
Hey, Beom-seok.
What's wrong?
Dude's being a dick 'cause Ahn Su-ho
and Yeon Si-eun are on his side.
What?
Hey, move.
What is it?
What's going on?
Hm?
- He flipped out for like no reason.
- Fuck you.
- I'm going to kill you, asshole.
- Hey, that's enough.
Enough. Hey.
What the fuck are you looking at?
- Huh, huh?
- Why do you keep trying to
be so tough? It's kinda cute.
Si-eun-a. Cafeteria. Food.
Stop putting your arm around me.
Huh?
What's gotten into him?
FUCKER 3
15 MISSED CALLS
16 MISSED CALLS
FUCKER 4
17 MISSED CALLS
How was it?
Feeling refreshed from your
early morning workout?
Did you get in touch with Oh Beom?
No.
Is there something going on with him?
He won't pick up his phone.
Wanna
swing by his place later?
Yeah, let's go see him.
All right.
Stand up.
You told me to just run.
- There's more?
- I said I'd give you a lesson.
Mm.
We'll do just the basics.
Stand with your feet shoulder width apart.
The tip of your feet point diagonally.
You can stop anytime.
You have to be tired.
Go home and sleep.
I'm not tired, don't worry.
Come on.
Make sure you always
tuck in your chin.
Okay?
Arms like this.
You have to use your arms to protect
your chin. At all times.
Don't forget.
Chin.
That's it.
Next, imagine
there's a punk in front of you.
He's threatening to beat you to death,
you're not gonna live, etcetera.
When this happens,
you don't want to look into his eyes.
Look at his shoulders, instead.
Watch me.
Keep your eyes on his shoulders.
Then,
when his shoulder comes toward your face,
duck below at a ninety-degree angle.
And then grab!
In this pose,
grab his knees and push him over.
One, two, three.
That's called a takedown.
The next step is to take
your fists and beat-
Nevermind.
Run.
It's better just to run.
Run away while the other guy's down.
Because you might get hurt fighting him.
Got it?
This is it?
He lives in a freaking nice place.
What are you guys doing here?
Dude, why did you turn your phone off?
Oh, I didn't know it was off.
Come in.
What about school?
Huh?
Why'd you no show?
Hmm?
Your place is sick.
I wasn't feeling well.
- Put those on.
- Nice.
This is probably why you're so thin.
Lose weight just walking
around your house.
This place is huge.
Is this the famous ZZ
plant that's supposed
to bring in a lot of money and wealth?
Hm?
This is amazing.
This room's gigantic.
Bigger than my house.
Do you feel really ill?
No, not too bad.
Just some.
Hey, your mother's really beautiful.
It's great seeing your family so happy.
You all look alike.
Hm.
We aren't family.
My father adopted me publicly
when he got into politics.
It was a publicity stunt.
You guys want a drink?
Is something wrong?
- No, nothing's wrong.
- Hey,
what is it?
Hmm?
It's okay.
You can tell me anything.
Maybe
is it because of those guys at karaoke?
Is it them?
Karaoke?
What karaoke?
Stay right there.
Hey, move over.
At ease.
- I said stand at ease, you freaking mutt.
- Hurry the hell up.
Did you forget?
- I told you to stand right.
- Here I come.
- Give it everything you got, okay?
- Show him what you've got, give it to him!
- Pow!
- Nice job!
Yes, that's it!
- Are you crying?
- This plebe.
- Fuck you.
- Are you crying?
- Stop pretending like it hurts.
- Hey, hey.
Beom-seok-a,
you better not tell your dad.
'Kay?
Hey, let's go.
It's no fucking fun beating him up.
I'm starving. Let's go get some food.
- Yeah, I'm hungry too.
- Ugh, that was so boring.
Total waste of time.
At my former school,
I was bullied.
And because of them,
I ended up in the hospital
and transferred schools to here.
But then ever since they
ran into me at karaoke.
They won't stop calling,
telling me to come out.
Oh, fuck.
Why'd those fucking assholes
do that to you?
Huh?
What did you even do wrong?
Sometimes it just happens.
In order to move up in
their group of friends,
they pick someone to bully.
What did I do wrong?
I didn't do anything to provoke it.
It's okay, Beom-seok-a.
It wasn't your fault.
Call those dickheads right now.
What?
I'll make them apologize to ya.
Give 'em a call.
Did you swallow a frog?
He's so freaking bad. Like the worst.
DOG BEOM-SEOK
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
- Ayy!
- Why did you turn it off?
- Aw, what the hell?
Our little Beom-seok's calling back.
- Oh, what?
- Seriously?
- Guys, shut up.
- Beom-seok-jjang?
- Damn it.
Hey, Beom-seok-a.
Where are ya?
Why are these pricks always at karaoke
when they should be studying.
You're really one to talk.
Don't be scared. I got you.
Beom-seok's here.
Hey, Oh Beom.
Beom-seok-a.
- You actually came.
- You brought your friends with you?
Fuck this, man.
- He's freaking scary.
- The fucking cigarettes reek.
What the hell's this?
Apologize.
Apologize to me.
- Right.
- You hear that?
- Apologize for what?
- For everything that you've done.
Hey, Beom-seok-a.
We apologize
when something we do is wrong.
We're friends, Beom-seok-a.
Aren't we?
I mean, we had fun together.
What's your deal?
Huh?
Hey.
Apologize correctly.
What?
How many times do we have to say it?
Apologize to him before I kick your ass,
okay?
Don't mess around.
Beom-seok-a.
What the fuck do you think
that you're doing?
Do you want to go back to being friends?
See each other every day?
Did you forget I was here?
- Hey, wait, wait a sec.
- Apologize to him properly.
- Okay, fine. I get it.
- Okay?
Answer me.
Okay, okay, okay. I said I fucking get it!
Agh.
Hey,
do it now.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
If you're sorry,
then let me hit you.
What?
You're bullshitting your apology to me,
so let me hit you.
Okay, then.
Let him hit you and move on.
Honestly,
really, truly, I'm so fucking super sorry,
alright, Beom-seok-a.
What the fuck.
You crazy shithead. Fuck you!
Hey, are you okay?
Hey.
Hey. Hey!
That's enough.
Don't cross the line.
Hey.
Hey!
- Enough's enough.
- Fuck, let go of me, you fucking asshole!
Let go of me, you bitch. Fucking asshole!
Fuck it. Come here, you shit for brains!
Fuck!
What the fuck was that?
None of you-
ever contact Beom-seok again.
Fuck.
Come here.
Hey, stop.
I can't br--
I can't breathe.
Okay, man. I'm sorry. Sorry.
Stop doing that!
Stop putting your arm around my shoulder.
Why do you fucking drag
me around everywhere?
What?
Why are you always ordering me around?
Huh?
Why do I fucking have to
stop because you decided?
Huh?
Those fucking assholes put
me through so much shit.
You have no idea.
- When have I ever ordered you around?
- You fucking order me
around every single day.
Do I have to stop when you tell me to?
Am I your fucking minion?
Hey.
Did I do something to you?
I skipped on my part-time
job to help you out.
Why the hell are you bitching?
- Unbelievable.
- Hey, come on.
"To help me out"?
You're patronizing me, seriously?
What, do you want me to pay
you for missing work?
- You're being a fucking asshole.
- Fuck!
Say that to me
one more time.
Try running your mouth again, you fuck.
Hey, let go and talk it out.
Huh?
Fuck this.
Hey, Beom-seok-a.
That nut job.
I'll go talk to him.
Beom-seok-a.
What's gotten in to you?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
See you later.
Your call cannot be completed as dialed.
This fucking asshole!
- What the hell is up with this, brah?
- You're such a dipshit.
Huh?
Oh Beom-seok?
You took your glasses off.
You uh,
hang out here too?
Hey, Oh Beom-seok!
Follow me.
Hey,
where you from?
- Mungang?
- Ahh.
Rich kids, right?
I said follow me,
- you fucking bastard.
- Man,
this wuss from Mungang is trying
to mess with Byuksan.
Wanna die?
I was so broke, but it's my lucky day!
Hey, how much you got?
Hey bro,
don't be scared. Let's have a quick chat.
I heard that one.
- Next in line.
- You prick.
Hey, raise your fucking head.
Sit upright, you dipshit.
Ooh.
You too. Lift your head up.
- Sit all the way up.
- Hey,
you should've fucking stuck to
your studies. Why pick a fight?
Fuck, okay time to pull out your phones.
Six, six, seven, five, zero, two.
One, one, eight, four, one, one, seven.
Lee Jeong-chan.
How much we get?
Damn it. I can't believe we found
a bunch of broke asses.
- I'm going to fucking kick your ass,
- That sucks.
Bitch.
You're the bitch! Asshole!
What the fuck are you looking at?
Huh?
Spit it out!
Do you have something to say,
fucking asshole?!
Son of a bitch. You fucking asshole.
Fuck you, asshole.
- He's totally lost it.
- Goddamn mother fucker.
If you're kicking his ass,
make sure you do it right. Go all in.
- Yeah?
- Asshole, fucking eat shit.
That's it.
- Little bro's goin' hard!
- Die, you stupid fucking shit fuck!
Fuck you.
Say that to my face one more time, fucker.
You done?
Let's go for a drink.
Sure.
Hey man, come on, dance!
That one?
- Damn, but the other girl was fugs.
- Go hit on someone.
We gotta get wasted to
hit on girls like that!
- You're right.
- How much money you guys have on you?
- I got nothing.
- None.
- How much did you get from those pricks?
- We're tapped out after
we pay for these drinks.
- Damn it.
- Hey,
Forget it.
There's too many of us to hit on girls.
Damn it, for real bro.
Drinks are on me. Order what you want.
- Woah.
- Bro, what? -Ohhhh.
So much money.
- Wow.
- My man.
- Oh.
- Oh Beom-seok.
- Go!
- Oh Beom-seok! -Sweet!
Everybody, everybody, selfie time.
- Hey, lift it up, show the cash!
- One, two, three.
Yeah!
- Nice shot! -Cheers!
- Cheers!
- Drink up!
- Yeah!
Start looking for pretty girls.
- Oh shit, five hundred thousand won.
- That's so much!
- Bro, do you like it?
- It's smooth!
- Yeah, it's good.
- Alright.
Rich drinks taste better.
Hm.
Beom-seok-a.
What's your IG?
So I can tag you.
Oh.
- I'll follow you if you follow me.
- Sure.
- All done.
- Cool.
Hey,
- over there.
- Yeah, where?
Oh! Hey,
come with me.
No, don't take him. Take him instead.
- I'm bad at this, I can't.
- Fuck it.
You.
Let's go.
- Ping!
- Make sure you succeed.
He's insane.
Hey, hey, hey. Forget him.
- Let's cheers. -Cheers,cheers,cheers.
- Cheers,cheers,cheers.
- Cheers.
- Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Wow dude, that's a lot.
- Ohhhh.
- Oh
Beom-seok,
you're going to get shit-faced.
Dude, that drink's so strong.
- Ohhhh.
- Woah.
- Oh Beom-seok!
- Let's get a girl for Beom-seok.
- Let's go!
Where's a girl that Beom-seok would like?
Shoo-
What about that one?
Oh yeah.
- Yeah.
- No, she's ugly.
You have fucking high standards.
- You turn everyone down.
- You're the weird one.
What about her?
Fuck. She's so pretty.
- That one.
- Wow.
Yeah.
Hey, hey, hey. What are you-?
- Wait, which one?
- Shhhh.
- Here are your drinks.
- Oh! Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Point her out.
- Where, where?
- Just go try!
They failed!
Hey!
- Salute.
- Fail.
- She humbled your ass.
- What the heck was that?
- Come on.
- Nah, nah, nah. When I saw her
up close, she wasn't my type.
- Did you even try?
- No, she was fucking ugly.
- Forget it.
- Yeah right, he couldn't fucking get
- a word out when we went over there.
- Come here loser who couldn't say a word.
Damn. Give up.
- Have another drink.
- Hey, can you pour me a lot of beer?
- Woah, I'm kinda lit.
- No way. -I'm think I'm reaching my limit.
You can't be drunk already.
Hm?
Where is he going?
- Where are you going?
- Bro!
- Where's he going?
- Beom-seok-a!
Wanna party?
What?
Come party with us.
- What?
- Bro!
- Oh what!
- Oh.
- Bro's got more rizz than you do!
- Oooh.
ALL NAMES, PLACES, AND EVENTS SHOWN
ARE FICTIONAL
ANY SIMILARITY TO REALITY IS COINCIDENTAL